Nicholas Massarelli Graphic Design

> @nick.massarelli nickmassarelli.com nickmass93@gmail.com 508.769.6405 Brooklyn, New York

Last updated: January, 2022

Projects

First Last

A periodic artist publication, consisting of ten posters, folded into book form, showcasing the work of four artists per issue. Co-run with Sean Murray. www.firstlast.us.

Recent

I began teaching a five-week workshop at Parsons School of Design titled "X Quanitites."

IOTA Editions was announced, which I have been working on with Ian Shiver since 2019.

I was invited by Andrew McQuiston to lead a 1-day workshop for the Senior Studio students at the University of the Arts, Philadelphia.

Currently working independently on projects with Mish Mish Philadelphia, Brown University Arts Institute, HMWRK, Quickbooks, and Smog Press.

Education

Yale School of Art, New Haven, CT MFA in Graphic Design, 2021

Typography Summer School, London, UK, Summer 2017

Drexel University, Philadelphia, PA BS in Graphic Design, 2015

Work Experience

Actual Source Senior Designer, 2021-Current

Yale University Art Gallery Designer (part-time), 2019-2021

Philadelphia Museum of Art Graphic Designer, 2018-2019

Teaching Experience

X Quantities
Parsons School of Design
5-week workshop, Spring 2022
x.nickmassarelli.com

(TA) Advanced Graphic Design(TA) Intro to Graphic DesignYale University, 2020Taught by Henk van Assen

- (TA) Intro to Interactive Design Yale University, Summer 2020 Taught by Matt Wolff
- References and work samples are available upon request.